,Dear Sir or Madam

I am writing to express my interest in being considered as a candidate for any suitable position .within your firm

.With my experience I hope a great addition to your company

Throughout my career I have offered my clients a great customer service with a very well .understanding of my clients' needs and delivering what I promised

.I have established great relations with clients and co-workers based on trust and team work

I have the ability to work under pressure and meet deadlines with excellent communications and .personal skills

, If you would like to schedule an interview or otherwise discuss my interest in this position $% \left(1\right) =\left(1\right) \left(1\right)$

.Please call me at your convenience

.If you require any further information, please do not hesitate to contact me

I will be very pleased to meet you at your convenience and discuss my possible and valuable .contribution to your company. I am looking forward to hearing from you soon

Best Regards

Hossam Abou-Raya

Hossam Emam Abou-Raya



Email address: hosamabouraya11@gmail.com 19 Bnha st, Khatem El Morsalen st, Wimpy, Al Haram

Day Phone Number: +2 / 4505309

Mobile Phone Number: +2 / -- 01004450442

Career Objective

According to my experience and skills which has been shown below. I am seeking a suitable position as Hris Manager.

Summary

Eight years' and going experience as Application Consultant and. Furthermore, I am a hard worker, Self-motivated, target oriented, have wide Information Technology (Oracle for HCM modules) and experience of software implementation supported by business processes experience including Human Resources Management (HRMS), Software Project Management and Sql server

Education/Training

I have completed Hr Advanced Diploma 2018

I Have completed Sap R3 study of HCM configuration

March,2015

And key user which included in contents: -

(Organizational structure - Personnel administration - Time management -Payroll) at (Allied consulting) Supported by working on trial project.

Mini MBA in HCM & Project management, Ain-Shams University,

May, 2013

Grade: Excellent.

Bachelor of law, Cairo University, Grade: good.

May,2010

Professional Experience

HRIS ORACLE MANAGER: The United Bank from 2018 till now Senior AX consultant: BI - Technologies from 2017 till 2018

Senior HCM consultant: United of og from April 2017 till October 2017

HCM consultant supervisor: Implex from April 2015 till Abril 2017

- Restructured organizational hierarchies and aligned it with ERP processes.
- Ensured proper distribution and handling of data.
- Instructed and trained employees at site to adapt the changes in business process.
- Completed implementation of ERP system within time and minimal cost.
- Handled designing of applications, management of development group, pilot testing and deployment.
- Created user manuals for clients.
- Analyzing business models and assisting in upgrading ERP systems.
- Configuring complete practical ERP system.
- Testing and training staff on using ERP system.
- Redesigning business processes for increasing efficiency.
- Documenting and maintaining entire steps in testing, implementing and installing ERP system.
- Assessing ERP needs of clients and delivering in time.

Projects:

Travco group: full implementation

Tie: technical support

Saudi diesel: technical supportSiro misr : technical support

HCM Application Consultant: ITG Egypt from June 2013 till may, 2015

Provide functional implementation for human resources module including Personnel, Attendance, recruitment, Training, performance appraisal, payroll and Employee self-service ESS.

- Involved in all ERP implementation phases including; Gap Analysis, configuration,
 Prototype development, end user training, UAT execution and production.
- interviewing client's employees, management team and other stakeholders
- Conducting elicitation session analysis and presenting findings and recommendations to clients
- Develop SRS document and test case scenarios
- Identifying issues and forming solutions
- Contribute with operation team to synchronize requirements in order to avoid contradiction and setup integration scenario.
- Designing and develop prototypes as per SRS
- Performs application configuration using application tools
- Provide on-site training for client's employees
- Contribute with customer to execute acceptance test cases

Key Achievements/ selected Projects

- Final completion of SAP R3 (HCM) configuration to do with the team work in the training project to simulate the practical reality in SAP implementation.
- I have been awarded by PMO for process re-engineering made for two clients had business pain 6 months of my hiring.

List of latest 4 project in the role of Application Consultant.

- Tayseer Mardini for Textile manufacturing.
- Maytrade for Chemicals and fertilizers.
- Headline Printing House.
- Light-way for led electricity manufacturing.

Skills

Computer Skills

- I have wide knowledge about SAP R3 (HCM) configuration and key user (organizational structure - personnel administration - time management -payroll), Background about reporting for each module.
- Experience using Microsoft products including Microsoft Office2003 & 2007, Microsoft Windows, project management tools like Microsoft Project.
- I have ability to learn new systems, techniques, technologies in a very short time.

Management Skills

- Talent management
- Supply chain management
- Project management
- Leadership management
- Ethics of business
- Strategies principles
- Marketing management
- Business process

Personal Skills

- Alerted, focused,
- Very good communicator
- Very good presenter
- Issues solver
- Dreamer
- Enthusiastic
- Persuasive and Visionary

Prefer Multitasks

Languages

Arabic : Mother TongueEnglish : Very Good

References

Are ready under request